大卫·马兰：大家好 世界
DAVID MALAN: Hello, world.
我是大卫·马兰 这是CS50的S介绍
My name is David Malan, and this is CS50's Introduction
到使用Python语言编程
to Programming with Python.
而CS50本身就是对知识型企业的介绍
Whereas CS50 itself is an introduction to the intellectual enterprises
计算机科学和编程艺术
of computer science and the art of programming,
本课程特别侧重于使用Python本身进行编程
this course is specifically focused on programming in Python itself.
在课程开始时 我们将专注于
At the beginning of the course, we'll be focused
关于编程中的一个主题 称为函数和变量、机制
on a topic in programming known as functions and variables, mechanisms
通过它 您可以编写解决较小问题的代码
via which you can write code that solves smaller problems,
但您可以将这些较小的解决方案组合成解决方案
but you can compose those smaller solutions into solutions
更大的问题
to larger problems still.
然后我们将过渡到条件句
We'll then transition to a look at conditionals,
一种用代码逻辑表达自己的方式 可能会做一些事情
a way in code of expressing yourself logically, to maybe do something
如果某个问题的答案是真的 或者不是
if some question has an answer of true, or not
如果答案是假的 就做点什么
do something if the answer is false.
之后我们会过渡到介绍你
We'll transition thereafter to introducing you
循环 在代码中 一次又一次地做某事的能力
to loops, the ability, in code, to do something again, and again,
一次又一次
and again some number of times.
然后我们将过渡到更具技术性的东西
We'll then transition to something a little more technical,
被称为例外情况
known as exceptions.
不幸的是 在编写代码时可能会出现很多错误 其中一些
Unfortunately, a lot can go wrong when you're writing code, some of it
你的错 其中一些可能是别人的错
your fault, some of it perhaps someone else's fault.
但可以说 您可以编写防御性代码 并且实际上
But you can write code defensively, so to speak, and actually
捕捉那些类型的异常 那些错误
catch those kinds of exceptions, those errors,
并正确处理它们 以便您为其编写代码的用户
and handle them properly so that the users you're writing code for
实际上 我看不到同样的东西
don't actually see the same.
此后 我们将看看库、第三方代码、
Thereafter, we'll take a look at libraries, third-party code,
通常是别人写的 也可能是你自己写的
written by other people, often, or perhaps yourself in the past,
可以在您自己的项目中使用和重复使用的
that you can use and reuse in your own projects
以避免一次又一次地重复发明轮子
so as to avoid reinventing the wheel again and again.
之后 我们将介绍一种称为单元测试的东西
We'll look thereafter at something called unit tests.
事实证明 您实际上将编写代码来测试您自己的代码
It turns out, you'll actually write code to test your own code.
但是您不必为您的测试编写测试
But you won't have to write tests for your tests.
事实上 这是业界的最佳实践 为代码编写测试
Indeed, this is a best practice in industry, writing tests for your code
因此 您可以肯定您今天的代码是 希望是
so that one, you can be sure that your code today is, hopefully,
如果您的测试是正确的 请自行更正
if your tests are correct, correct itself.
而且 如果您或其他人明天或以后修改您的代码
But moreover, if you or someone else modifies your code tomorrow, or down
您可以重新运行相同的测试以确保
the line, you can rerun those same tests to ensure
这些新的更改没有破坏您自己的代码的任何内容
that those new changes have not broken anything about your own code.
然后我们将看一看一种叫做
We'll then take a look at something called
文件I/O、用于输入和输出的I/O、能力
File I/O, I/O for input and output, the ability
不仅要将信息存储在计算机的内存中
to not just store information inside of a computer's memory,
而是持久地将其保存到磁盘 可以说 保存到文件和文件夹
but rather save it persistently to disk, so to speak, to files and folders.
然后我们来看一下另一种技术 即
We'll then take a look at another technique, known
作为正则表达式 因此 在Python中 您可以定义模式
as regular expressions, whereby, in Python, you can define patterns
你可以验证数据 以确保人类在你输入的时候输入一些东西
and you can validate data to make sure the human typed something in as you
期待吧
expect.
或许 您可以使用正则表达式来提取数据
You can use regular expressions to extract data, perhaps
从你想要分析的某个数据集
from some data set you're trying to analyze.
然后 我们将最终了解面向对象编程
We'll then take a look, ultimately, at object-oriented programming,
一种范例 一种编写代码的方式 由此你可以用代码来表示
a paradigm, a way of writing code, whereby you can represent, in code,
真实世界的实体
real-world entities.
这是对其他编程范例的补充 我们将
And this is in addition to other paradigms of programming that we'll
还探索了其中的过程性编程
also explore, among them procedural programming,
在那里你可以编写很多这样的函数、过程
where you write lots of those functions, procedures
真的 从上到下 一步一步地解决问题
really, top to bottom, to solve problems step by step,
甚至还有一些被称为函数式编程的东西
and even something known as functional programming, as well.
然后在课程的最后 我们将
And then at the very end of the course will we
为你的工具箱配备更多的工具
equip you with all the more tools for your toolkit.
和更多的构建块 更多的词汇
and additional building blocks, additional vocabulary
通过它 在同样的课程结束后 你可以自己走
via which, after this same course, you can go off on your own
或者参加其他课程 或者自己解决项目
and either take other courses or solve projects of your own,
使用所有这些机制
using all of these mechanisms.
现在 本课程本身假定没有以前的编程背景
Now this course itself assumes no prior programming background.
因此 您不需要用Python编写一行代码
So you don't have to have written a single line of code in Python,
或任何语言 目前还没有
or any language, yet.
但这也是一门您可以在CS50之前、期间甚至之后学习的课程
But this is also a course that you can take before, during, or even after CS50
如果你想更精通Python 那就可以了
itself, if you'd like to get all the more versed with Python.
每周 通过课程讲座
Each week, via the courses lectures, will we introduce you
我们将
to any number of concepts that we'll then
每周以习题集的形式进行更深入的探究
drill down more deeply into in the form of problem sets each week.
也就是说 编程项目
That is, programming projects that will enable
你应该把学到的一些东西应用到你自己的问题上
you to apply some of those lessons learned to problems of your very own.
在课程结束的时候 你会有
And by the end of the course, you'll have
解决了很多问题 理想情况下
solved so many problems that, ideally, are representative
你最终会在现实世界中遇到的问题
of problems you'll eventually encounter in the real world,
无论你是否渴望在技术世界中解决代码问题
whether you aspire to solve code in the technical world
或者艺术 人文 社会科学
or perhaps in the arts, the humanities, the social sciences,
自然科学 或超越
the natural sciences, or beyond.
你最终会拥有词汇量和技术技能
You'll have, ultimately, the vocabulary and the technical skills
通过它来接近同样的东西
via which to approach the same.
这就是CS50
This, then, is CS50.
这是CS50的Introduction to Programming with Python
And this is CS50's Introduction to Programming with Python.